A Guide to the ODU Poster Collection, 1974-1990
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- ODU Organizations 1977-1984, 1986-1988
  - Student and Alumni Organizations 1977-1981, 1984, 1986, 1988
    - Student Activities Calendar & Information Guide 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5:147)
    - Student Organizations Manual, Office of Student Activities 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5:148)
    - Telephone Campaign (Box-folder 5:149)
    - The Circle K Order (Box-folder 5:150)
    - The Head Stone Circus, fragile (Box-folder 5:150)
    - Volunteerism: Something for you, something for others, ODU Student Affairs & Voluntary Outreach Center, fragile (Box-folder 5:151)
    - Volunteer Day, Volunteer Outreach Center, fragile (Box-folder 5:152)
- University Sponsored Community Events 1975-1985
  Contains posters for University wide events, events for the general public or events sponsored with other organizations.
  - 4th Annual Symposium on Mental Health & the Law, UVA 1980 (Box-folder 6:1)
  - A Conference with the U.S. Secretaries of State (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Adventure into Faith with Canon Bryan Green, D.D., Episcopal Churches of Tidewater and Canterbury House (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Affirmative Action Awareness Seminars (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Alexander Markov Paganini: Twenty-four Caprices (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Angela Davis 1984 (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Architecture & The North American City 1980 (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Bounty Rainbow Programs -- Toad of Toad Hall 1977 (Box-folder 6:8)
  - CIA -- William Colby 1976 (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Colloquium III: Libraries & the History & Criticism of the Arts 1979 (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Colonies in Space? Sigma Xi (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Community Arts Program -- Jazz Showcase 1980 (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Community Arts Program -- The Path: Experiences from Being Black 1980 (Box-folder 6:13)
  - Community Services Program -- Count Basie & His Orchestra (Box-folder 6:14)
  - Community Services Program -- Something About the Music (Box-folder 6:15)
  - Dick Gregory Bares His Soul (Box-folder 6:16)
  - Donald Bogle on the Image of Blacks in the Movies (Box-folder 6:17)
  - Dr. Benjamin Hooks 1978 (Box-folder 6:18)
  - Drawing (Box-folder 6:19)
  - Eastern Virginia Conference on Human Sexuality (Box-folder 6:20)
  - Edmond Burke and the American Revolution, Bicentennial Lecture (Box-folder 6:21)
  - Eleanor Holmes Norton, Black History Month Committee 1982 (Box-folder 6:22)
  - Environmental Hazards: Man Made and Man Remedied by Ralph Nader (Box-folder 6:23)
  - First Hellenic Conference: Greece Yesterday, Today, Tomorrow 1978 (Box-folder 6:24)
  - Flo Kennedy 1981 (Box-folder 6:25)
  - Founders Day Convocation (Box-folder 6:26)
  - Freedoms and Responsibilities of the Press, Cultural Events and Convocation Committee 1982 (Box-folder 6:27)
  - George Manson in the VA Convention of 1776: lecture by Helen Hill Miller, The ODU Bicentennial Committee (Box-folder 6:28)
  - Glennan Lecture Series, Responsibility and the Media (Box-folder 6:29)
  - Glennan Lecture Series, The Government & the Press: A Constitutional Conflict (Box-folder 6:30)
  - Glennan Lecture Series, The View From Washington (Box-folder 6:31)
  - Grammar 101: Lilac & Tractor A Rock Concert (Box-folder 6:32)
  - Hypnosis -- Legal, Clinical, and Research Application 1980 (Box-folder 6:33)
  - Justice in America by William Kunstler 1977 (Box-folder 6:34)
  - Kristin Lems Live! (Box-folder 6:35)
  - Lisel Mueller: Poet 1975 (Box-folder 6:36)
  - Man and Dance sponsored by the Brotherhood of Metropolitan AME Church (Box-folder 6:37)
  - Maria Benitez -- Spanish Dance Company 1978 (Box-folder 6:38)
  - Mary, Queen of Scots -- Virginia Opera Association 1978 (Box-folder 6:39)
  - Mayakovsky, Poet (Box-folder 6:40)
  - NRBQ and The Whole Wheat Horns, 2 (Box-folder 6:41)
  - ODU & NSU Present: The Olatunji Dance Troupe 1981 (Box-folder 6:42)
  - ODU: New Dominions (Box-folder 6:43)
  - Our Environmental Outlook: Gloom or Boom? 1985 (Box-folder 6:44)
  - Peace & War: Time to Make a Choice (Box-folder 6:45)
  - Photographs, Airbrush and More by Mike Ostrander (Box-folder 6:46)
  - Ramsey Lewis -- Jazz Show (Box-folder 6:47)
  - Rev. Ralph Abernathy 1979 (Box-folder 6:48)
  - Role of the Urban University: Present and Future (Box-folder 6:49)
  - Roots, Rock, Reggae 1981 (Box-folder 6:50)
  - Senator Sam Ervin (Box-folder 6:51)
  - Soon and Very Soon: A Celebrations of a Peoples Culture (Box-folder 6:52)
  - Southern Women: What We Know and What We Would Like to Know (Box-folder 6:53)
  - Spring Calendar of Events (Box-folder 6:54)
  - The Inchon Landing 25 Years ago & Old Norfolk Scenes (Box-folder 6:55)
  - The Manson Murders by Vincent Buliosi (Box-folder 6:56)
  - The Mis-Education of the Negro (Box-folder 6:57)
  - The Tempest (Box-folder 6:58)
  - Tidewaters Marine Environment, VA Museum of Marine Sciences 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6:59)
  - United Way Funday, United Way (Box-folder 6:60)
  - Urban South, 3rd Annual Conference 1977 (Box-folder 6:61)
  - Urban South, 4th Annual Conference 1978 (Box-folder 6:62)
  - Urban South, 5th Annual Conference 1979 (Box-folder 6:63)
  - Urban South, 6th Annual Conference 1980 (Box-folder 6:64)
  - Urban South, 7th Annual Conference, ODU & NSU 1981 (Box-folder 6:65)
  - Urban South, Virginia Conference on Urban Studies (Box-folder 6:66)
  - Who Killed Kennedy? by Mark Lane 1977 (Box-folder 6:67)
  - World Sovereignty: Will the Nation-State Survive? (Box-folder 6:68)
  - Your University in the Computer Age 1983 (Box-folder 6:69)
- Athletics 1978-1982, 1986, 1988-1989
  Contains poster on general athletic topics, Basketball, Soccer, Summer Camp, Tennis, and Wrestling.
  - General 1979, 1986
    - Big Blue Day 1979 (Box-folder 7:1)
    - ODU Monarchs: Athletics Poster/Collage (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Support Old Dominion University Athletics 1986 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Old Dominion University Department of Intercollegiate Athletics Citation (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Virginia Intercollegiate State Championship -- Blank Brackets (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Basketball 1979-1981, 1988-1989
    - Big Blue Basketball -- Mens & Womens Game Schedule (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Big Blue Magic Mens Basketball 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Big Blue Magic Womens Basketball 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Corporate Opportunities Old Dominion University Basketball 1988-1989 (Box-folder 7:9)
    - De Paul Who? 1981 (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Soccer 1979, 1988-1989
    - Announcing Soccer: Kiwanis Classic (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Big Blue Magic Fall Sports: Soccer & Field Hockey 1979 (Box-folder 7:12)
    - Met Life Soccer Classic 1988, 2 sizes (Box-folder 7:13)
    - Met Life Soccer Classic 1989 (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Summer Camp 1983, 1986
    - Summer Camps & Clinics 1983 (Box-folder 7:15)
    - ODU Summer Camps 1986 (Box-folder 7:16)
  - Tennis 1979-1982
    - 2nd Annual Miltons Pizza Tennis Classic 1979 (Box-folder 7:17)
    - 3rd Annual Miltons Pizza Tennis Classic 1980 (Box-folder 7:18)
    - 4th Annual Mixed Doubles Tennis Tournament 1980 (Box-folder 7:19)
    - 5th Annual Mixed Doubles Tennis Tournament 1981 (Box-folder 7:20)
    - 6th Annual Mixed Doubles Tournament 1982 (Box-folder 7:21)
    - 6th Annual Mens Scholarship Tennis Tournament: Big Blue Banana Classic 1981 (Box-folder 7:22)
    - Kitchen Towne 2nd Annual Womens Tennis Classic (Box-folder 7:23)
    - Kitchen Towne 3rd Annual Womens Tennis Classic 1979 (Box-folder 7:24)
    - Kitchen Towne 5th Annual Womens Tennis Classic & Husband-and-Wife Doubles 1981 (Box-folder 7:25)
  - Wrestling 1978
    - 7th Annual Civitan-Monarch Wrestling Classic 1979 (Box-folder 7:26)